Guide to the Tom Burrell papers, 1949-2016 and undated RL.11678
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2015 and undated; 6
  - Tom Burrell presentation, 2000 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11678-VHS-019)
  - Burrell PR video 3:45, 1998 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11678-Bcam-001)
  - Burrell congratulations, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11678-Bcam-002)
  - Study Buddies, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11678-Bcam-003)
  - 25 anniversary Black United Fund of Illinois; Living Legends/Passing the Torch Awards Benefit Gala, Chicago; 7:30, 2010 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-001)
    Tom Burrell presentation
  - 56th Advertising Hall of Fame, 2005 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-002)
  - America I Am celebration video, 8:16, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-003)
  - Burrell--2005 YTD Television reel (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-004)
    Includes: McDonald's (Baobab, Screamers, Patio, Demo/Essence, Therapy; Toyota Stubs; Sears (Fresh Ideas, What Do You Give?); Crest Karaoke; Verizon Tech Makeover
  - Burrell--Historical montage, 2016 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-005)
  - Burrell--Montage with NBA players, 2010 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-006)
  - Burrell--Sprite hip hop spots, 2009 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-007)
    Includes: My Sprite and Me (Heavy D); Kid n Play; Kriss Kross; Voltron campaign 5 spots; Freestylin'/Puba Large; Rhyme for Rhyme; Court Rap; Lost Boys; Five Deadly Women campaign 5 spots; The Bust campaign 5 spots
  - Burrell--Top 10 commercials, 2013 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-008)
  - Buy Now Pay Later, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-009)
  - Dunkin Donuts, 2007 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-010)
    Bacon Lovers Supreme Omelet; J. Dupri Doesn't Give Customer a Ticket; WAGA Atlanta
  - Emory, Sears presentation, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-011)
  - Exit video; Last Two Dollars; 2:00, 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-012)
  - McDonald's: 4 track demo roughs, 2003 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-013)
    Includes: Lunch Time Jigg; Good Stuff; Big Mac
  - McDonald's: Presentation tracks, 2003 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-014)
    Includes: Dixie Chickens; I'm Lovin' It; Spice It Up; Me and the Guys; Morning Sunrise; Love Song; Lunch Time Jigg; Rock Star Wannabe; Why I'm Lovin' It; Triathlon; Classical; Lil' Jack; Mac Matrix
  - Paul D. Schrage Award, 2011 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-015)
    Tom Burrell, Marketing Excellence Lifetime Achievement Award
  - Sears Diversity Days, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-016)
  - Tide: Nostalgia/Dad :30, 2010 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-017)
  - Tom Burrrell interview, Library of Congress, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-018)
  - Tom Burrell old chapters disc 1, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-019)
  - Tom Burrell old chapters disc 2, undated (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-020)
  - Tom Burrell--One on one with 2012 New York Festivals Hall of Fame Inductee (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-021)
  - Toyota Rav4 QuickTimes: Good Day :30; The Journey :30, 2011 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-022)
  - Tribute video 1--Oprah, 2:20, 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-023)
  - Tribute video 2--Susan Taylor, 2:11, 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-024)
  - Tribute video 3--Roland Burris, 2:16, 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-025)
  - Tribute video 4--Rose/Farrakhan, 1:54, 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-026)
  - Video birthday greeting, Rev. Jesse L. Jackson Sr., 2015 (Box AV2, Optical-disc RL11678-OP-027)
  - Burrell exhibit at MBA, 1995 (Box AV2, Disk RL11678-FL3-001)
  - Mobil frame 1, undated (Box AV2, Disk RL11678-FL3-002)
  - Mobil frame 2, undated (Box AV2, Disk RL11678-FL3-003)
  - Coca-Cola, Sprite, stills, tiff files, 1997 (Box AV2, Disk RL11678-FL5-001)
  - Evelyn Burrell centennial birthday slideshow (Powerpoint), 2015 (Box AV2, Disk RL11678-USB-001)